wwar.com 2003-06-18

# Privacy Policy - World Wide Arts Resources, Corporation

**PRIVACY POLICY:**

World Wide Arts Resources / absolutearts.com are committed to safeguard your privacy online at any of our sites. Please be so kind as to read the following information to gain a better understanding of how your information will be used by World Wide Arts Resources. World Wide Arts Resources / absolutearts.com hereafter referred to as World Wide Arts Resources adheres to OPA Privacy standards. As the Internet and World Wide Arts Resources develop this policy might change. We do encourage you to return again to see if there have been any changes to our privacy policy. To assure you that we keep your data secure World Wide Arts Resources has not changed its privacy policy since 1996. 

**What personal information does World Wide Arts Resources collect?**   
World Wide Arts Resources collects information in several ways. Personal information is gathered from our clients when registering a website, for art news, artist portfolio, gallery portfolio or resources with our registration services. When purchasing any of the products offered by World Wide Arts Resources some personal information is gathered for processing purposes and to better serve our client. The more accurate the information provided the better our services will be. 

**How does World Wide Arts Resources use my Information?**  
World Wide Arts Resources uses all your information in a responsible manner! We use the information internally to be able to better serve you. We might send you an announcement of new or improved services at wwar.com. We might classify your records according to where your resource is located to better serve out visitors in terms of geographic location. World Wide Arts Resources might use your personal information for advertising targeting on our site to better serve your interests. If an adversiter requests for example to show advertisements to users from New York City we target the ad towards you if you live in New York and surrounding areas. However, we do **NOT** make your personal information available to the advertiser. Your information is safe with us! 

**Does World Wide Arts Resources sell my Information?**  
World Wide Arts Resources **DOES NOT SELL, RENT OR RELEASE PERSONAL INFORMATION GATHERED ON OUR SITES TO OTHER COMPANIES, INDIVIDUALS OR GROUPS!** Any information gathered is only used at World wide Arts Resources for purposes stated above. 

**How secure are my Transactions at World Wide Arts Resources?**   
World Wide Arts Resources uses industry standard secure server software. Should the client provide us with sensitive information for any reason (such as a credit card number), that information will be encrypted with industry standard SSL (Secure Socket Layer) technology. Please note that email is not encrypted and is not considered a secure means of transmitting credit card numbers. 

**World Wide Arts Resources and Third Party Advertising**  
Our websites sometimes uses a reputable third party to serve certain portions of advertisements that you see on the pages of our Web site. If you would like to know more about the information gathering practices and "opt-out" procedures of our third party ad server, please click here <http://www.sonar.com/content/privacy.htm>.

**What else you need to know about your privacy?**   
Please keep in mind that whenever you voluntarily disclose personal information online - for example on message boards, through email, or in chat areas - that information can be collected and used by others. In short, if you post personal information online that is accessible to the public, you may receive unsolicited messages from other parties in return. Ultimately, you are solely responsible for maintaining the secrecy of your passwords and/or any account information. Please be careful and responsible whenever you're online.
